Monica, which of all of this
kitchen stuff is mine?
모니카, 이 주방용품 중에서
내 건 뭐가 있지?
This bottle opener.
이 병따개
-And...?
-And it's a magnet.
또?
또 거기 붙은 자석
Look at that!
이거 봐
How weird is that?
You're moving in with me...
거참 신기하다
네가 우리 집에 유일하게
없는 물건을 갖고 들어오다니
and you have the one thing
I don't have.
It's like, in a way,
you complete me.
어떻게 보면 이로써
내가 완성되는 거야
-Kitchen.
-What?
- 주방 말이야
- 뭐?
네가 우리 주방을
완성시킨다고, 친구
You complete me kitchen, matey!
I know what you're thinking.
- 로스, 네 속셈 알겠다
- 뭘?
That she'll move in with you, then
fall in love with you, and then...
같이 살다가 레이첼이
다시 널 사랑하게 되고
when she finds out you're already
married, she'll be happy.
그때 결혼 사실을 알면
행복해질 거라 이거지?
You know? You're just very sad.
이 가련한 인생아
Oh, my God!
오 마이 갓!
이제야 알겠다
I see what this is.
You are in love with Rachel!
바로 네가 레이첼을
사랑하는 거야
- 뭐야?
- 이제야 설명이 되는군
It all adds up! You're obsessed
with her. It's always:
넌 레이첼한테 빠졌어
항상 그랬잖아
'로스, 레이첼 어떡할래?'
"What will you do about Rachel?
Why are you moving in with Rachel?
'로스, 왜 레이첼이랑 살지?'
'결혼 얘기는 언제 털어놓을래?'
When will you confess your secret
marriage to Rachel?" You want her!
넌 레이첼을 원하고 있어
아냐
오, 전화 덕분에 살았다
Saved by the bell.
여보셔?
Aren't these candlesticks mine?
레이첼, 이 촛대 내 거니?
No, I bought those.
아냐, 내가 샀잖아
Oh, right. I forgot.
- 맞다, 깜빡했네
- 그래
That you're a liar!
네가 거짓말쟁이란 걸
아뇨, 좋습니다
월요일에 가죠
That's great! I'll be there Monday.
And thank you again.
정말 감사합니다
고생물학과 학과장이야
That was the head
of the paleontology department...
at N...
뉴... 욕... 대학의
Y...
U.
그래서... 무슨...
얘길... 했는데?
Wow. What...
did he...
say?
내가 작년에 출간했던
퇴적층에 관한 논문 있지?
Remember that paper I had published
last year on sediment flow rate?
-They loved it.
-Well, who wouldn't?
- 그게 마음에 든대
- 누군 안 좋겠어
I know!
그렇지
Anyway, they asked me
to be a guest lecturer.
하여튼 날 강사로 초빙했어
It's temporary, but if they like me,
it could lead to a full-time job.
임시로 맡았지만 잘하면
정식교수가 될 수도 있지
How great would that look
on the mailbox? Professor Geller.
우편함에 이렇게 적으면
근사할 거야, '겔러 교수'
그래, 교수와 사모님
Professor and Mrs.
And Mrs.?
사모님이라니?
그래, 너랑 로스는 아직 부부야
You and Ross are still married.
What?
뭐?
Just kidding!
농담이야
놀래라
Oh, God!
간 떨어지겠네
Saved your ass.
불쌍해서 봐줬다
The One Where Joey Loses His lnsurance
- 왔니?
- 그래
- 어서 와
- 무슨 일이야?
What's the matter?
- 내 단골 심령술사 있지?
- 그래
You know that psychic I see?
She told me I'm gonna die this week,
so I'm bummed.
내가 이번 주에 죽을 거래
그래서 쇼크 먹었어
- 뭐야?
- 너흰 그런 거 잘 모르겠지만
I know you don't know about readings,
but that's the worst you can get.
이건 정말 최악의 점괘야
That's crazy.
너무 심하다
어떻게 그런 말을 해?
She'd say that to you?
그걸 믿는 건 아니겠지?
You don't believe her, do you?
세쌍둥이 얘기도 맞혔어
I don't know. She said
that I'd have triplets...
but she also said one of them
would be black.
하나는 흑인이라고 했지만
혹시 어떻게 죽을 거란
얘기도 했어?
Just out of curiosity,
did she say how you'd go?
아니, 죽는다는 얘기도
막판에 가서 하더라고
She didn't tell me I'd die
till the end of the session.
I wasn't gonna waste
a whole other hour there!
거기서 더 시간을 낭비할 순 없지
일주일밖에 안 남았는데
I've only got a week left.
I've really gotta start living now!
이제부터 제대로 살 거야
- 안녕, 얘들아
- 어서 와
Hey, everyone.
오늘이 내 첫 강의인데
Well, today's my first lecture...
너희들 앞에서 연습을
해보고 싶어, 괜찮겠니?
and I wanted to try it out
on you guys. Do you mind?
No, that'd be great!
좋지, 해봐라
그래
"There are three primary theories
concerning sediment flow rate.
퇴적층 유동에 관한 이론은
크게 세 가지로 나눠지는데
Each of these theories can be further
subcategorized into two..."
각각의 이론은 두 가지
하위범주로 구분됩니다
바로 이게 날 죽이는구나
This is it.
This is what's gonna kill me.
"...subcategories. The first
of these subcategories is.."
그리고 이 같은 하위범주의
첫 번째 이론을 살펴보면...
잠깐, 로스
Are there naked chicks
on that piece of paper?
거기 여자 알몸사진 있냐?
No. Why?
아니, 왜?
하도 뚫어져라 쳐다봐서
누드사진인 줄 알았다
I never seen a guy stare so hard at
something that didn't have chicks on it.
맞아, 그렇구나
"There are three primary theories...
퇴적층 유동에 관한 이론은...
concerning sediment flow rate.
크게 세 가지로 나눠지는데...
Each of these theories...
각각의 이론은 두 가지
하위범주로 구분됩니다
can be further subcategorized...
into.."
Why don't you open with a joke?
조크로 시작하는 건 어때?
Open with a joke?
It's a university, not a comedy club.
조크로 시작해?
이건 강의지 코미디가 아냐
그쯤 해서 대기
Wait a minute, hold the phone.
You're not talking
about Chuckles University?
'봉숭아학당'이 아니었어?
알았다
아냐, 농담이야
Come on, we're kidding.
You know what might make it
less boring?
따분하지 않게
하는 방법이 있어
고맙다
Thank you.
Some visual aids.
영상자료 같은 건 어때?
오호라! 기막힌 게 있다
-You know what's a good visual aid?
-Don't say naked chicks.
알몸 여자라면 관두셔
Why not?
왜 안 돼?
I don't even know why I talk
to you guys about it.
공연히 너희들 시간만
뺏은 거 같다
I'm just gonna do it on my own,
with no naked chicks.
나 혼자 하겠어
알몸 여자 없이
나도 19살 때까지
그렇게 놀았어
That's the way I did it
till I was 19.
All right, 20.
그래, 20살
Twenty-three.
23살
- 나 왔어
- 그래
Any good mail?
좋은 소식 있어?
그래, 배우조합에서 왔네
Something from
the Screen Actors Guild.
It's probably a residual check.
Can you open it? I got....
아마 재방송 수당일 거야
대신 봐줄래? 난 바빠서
"Benefits lapsed."
'보험급여중지'
That's weird.
그거 이상하군
I don't remember being in a movie
called Benefits Lapsed.
'보험급여중지'란 영화에
출연한 기억이 없는데
이건 수표가 아냐
건강보험이 말소됐어
It's not a check. Your health
insurance expired because...
-you didn't work enough last year.
-Let me see that.
작년에 일을 많이 못했잖아
- 어디 보자
- 그래
Oh, I can't believe this!
이럴 수가
This sucks!
환장하겠네
When I had insurance,
I could get hit by a bus...
전엔 버스에 치이거나
불이 나도 괜찮았는데
or catch on fire, you know?
안 그래? 근데 이젠
몸조심해야 되는 거야?
And it wouldn't matter.
Now I gotta be careful?
I'm sorry. There's never
a good time to have to...
유감이다, 하필 이런 때
불을 내면 안 된다니
stop catching on fire.
All right, well...
좋아
I guess I gotta go see my agent.
일거리를 찾아야겠다
매니저한테 갔다 올게
Make sure to look both ways
before you cross the street.
길 건널 때 좌우를 잘 살펴라
"Make sure to look both ways
before you cross the street."
'길 건널 때 좌우를 잘 살펴라'
- 나 왔어
- 피비, 아직 살아있었네?
Hey, you're still alive!
How are you feeling?
기분은 어때?
죽음을 기다리는 게
너무 힘들다
It's so exhausting, waiting for death.
Oh, by the way, do you think you..
근데 너 혹시....
What are you doing?
지금 뭐하는 거야?
Preparing you for..
Didn't you think I was dead?
미리 준비를 하라고...
내 연기가 그렇게 형편없어?
Did that not come off?
Yeah, scared the hell out of me.
I thought we'd lost you forever.
아니, 널 잃을까봐
너무 무서웠어
-You wanna lie down?
-Yeah, thanks.
피비, 좀 누울래?
그래, 고마워
Can you do me a favor?
부탁 하나만 들어줄래?
Wake me up in a couple hours.
두어 시간 있다 깨워 줘
깨울 수 있으면
You know, if you can.
모니카
Did you take these back?
이거 도로 챙겨 넣었니?
아냐, 너무 맘에 들어서
내가 나가서 사온 거야
I liked them so much
that I bought some for myself.
그래, 정말 괜찮지?
They're really great, aren't they?
I love them.
아주 좋아
Nice try.
웃기고 있어 아주
얘들아
오빠, 강의는 어땠어?
How'd the lecture go?
대성공이야
It went great.
And I didn't need any jokes
or naked chicks either.
조크나 알몸 여자가
어딜 나서나
That's great. I'm sorry
we weren't supportive before.
잘됐다, 아까는 도움이
못 돼서 미안해
충실한 자료준비가 말을 했지
I knew I just had to let
the material speak for itself.
Everyone's all, "Ross, you have
to be funny and sexy."
'재미있고 섹시하게 나가라?
웃기지 말라 그래'
Well, I proved them wrong!
And now I'm gonna pass
the news on to Joey and Chandler.
조이랑 챈들러한테도
이 소식을 전해야겠다
오빠가 재미도 없고
섹시하지도 않다고?
-That you're not funny or sexy?
-That's right!
맞아
에스텔 레오나드
연기자 에이전시
-Hey, Estelle, listen..
-Well, well, well.
안녕하세요, 저기...
오호라...
Joey Tribbiani.
조이 트리비아니
So you came back, huh?
결국 돌아오셨구만, 어?
다들 제 잘난 줄 알지만
늘 에스텔 밑으로 기어 들어오지
They think they can do better,
but they all...
come crawling back to Estelle.
What are you talking about?
무슨 말씀이세요?
I never left you.
You've always been my agent.
저는 이 에이전시를
떠난 적이 없잖아요
Really?
그래?
네
Oh, well, no harm no foul.
그렇담 못 들은 걸로 해둬
Look, you gotta get me some work.
I lost my health insurance.
에스텔, 일거리가 필요해요
건강보험이 말소됐어요
All right, first thing we gotta do:
damage control.
좋아
먼저 피해대책부터 세우자고
왜요?
-Why?
-Well, I think...
글쎄, 내 생각엔
이 바닥의 누군가가...
someone out there...
may have been bad-mouthing you
all over town.
자네 험담을 하고
다닌 것 같아
The bastard!
빌어먹을 놈
뉴욕 대학
We're early.
The lecture doesn't end for 15 minutes.
좀 일찍 왔네
끝나려면 15분 남았어
- 살짝 들어가서 보자
- 그래, 좋아
-But we could sneak in and watch.
-Yeah, we could.
Hey, look. There's some
Kappa Kappa Deltas. I was a Kappa.
저길 좀 봐
'카파 카파 델타'야
나도 카파였는데
Hey, sisters.
안녕, 후배들?
Wow, we really are bitches.
졸지에 망할 년 되는군
Right. So when Rigby got his samples
back from the laboratory...
맞습니다, 연구실에서
표본을 가져온 릭비는
he made a startling discovery.
놀라운 발견을 하게 됩니다
화성암이라고 믿었던 돌이
실은 퇴적암이었던 것이죠
What he believed to be igneous
was, in fact, sedimentary.
Imagine his consternation when..
당시 그의 당혹감은...
Oh, bloody hell.
오호 통재라
- 나다
- 왔냐?
So Estelle lined up a bunch
of auditions for me tomorrow.
에스텔이 내일 오디션을
잔뜩 신청해놨거든
And I'll have my health insurance
back in no time.
곧 보험급여를
받을 수 있을 거야
그건 다행이다만...
That's great, but shouldn't you
be on the toilet right now?
너 화장실 안 가도 되냐?
뭐?
-What's wrong with you?
-Nothing.
왜 그러는데?
아냐
좀 전에 아령을 드는데
배가 끊어질 듯 아프잖아
I got this blinding pain in my stomach
when I was lifting weights before.
And then I passed out...
그래서 잠깐 까무러쳤지
그때부터 못 일어난 거야
and I haven't been able
to stand up since.
But I don't think
it's anything serious.
뭐 심각한 건 아니겠지
This sounds like a hernia.
Go to the doctor.
아무래도 탈장 같은데
병원에 가봐야지
무슨 소리
No way. If I go to the doctor, it'll be for
this thing sticking out of my stomach!
지금 내 배에서 삐져나오는
얘들을 치료한다면 모를까
That's a hernia.
그게 바로 탈장이야
Why'd I have to start
working out again?
괜히 또 운동을 시작했네
Damn you, 15s!
이 괘씸한 놈들아!
What the hell are you doing?
대체 뭐하는 거야?
Look, I was nervous.
너무 긴장을 했어
You guys had me all worried
I was gonna be boring.
따분하다면서 겁을 줬잖아
I got up there and they were
all, like, staring at me.
저기 올라가니까
다들 날 쳐다보는데
I opened my mouth and this
British accent just came out.
입을 여니까 영국식 억양이
튀어나오지 뭐야
Yeah, and not a very good one.
그렇게 좋지도 않던데?
Will you, please...?
목소리 좀 낮춰
Dr. Geller? Kurt Rathman.
겔러 박사, 커트 래스먼이오
I'm a paleontology professor here.
고생물학 교수죠
Do you have a moment
to talk about your lecture?
강의에 대해 얘기 좀 할까요?
I'm sorry, I've got plans
with my sister.
송구합니다만
누이와 약속이 있어서
Monica Geller.
'모니카 겔러르'예요
Right. Will you excuse us
for one moment?
네, 잠시만 실례하겠습니다
-What are you doing?
-You can have an accent, but I can't?
무슨 짓이야
나도 영국식으로 할 수 있어
Top of the morning to you, laddies!
명일에 봅세, 벗님들
Would you just please stop?
얘가 정말...
제발 그만해
Yes, yes, Bombay is very, very nice
this time of year.
네, 뭄바이는 지금이
아주 아주 좋답니다
Hey, will you grab me a cruller?
꽈배기도넛도 부탁할까?
앉아있어
Sit down!
병원에 안 갈 거야?
Will you go to the hospital?
야, 탈장 수술은 아마
돈이 많이 들 거야
Hernia operations cost...
a lot probably, okay?
게다가 날도 어두워지고 통증이
심해지는 걸 보니까 낫는 거야
Besides, it's getting darker and more
painful. That means it's healing.
Look, I'll loan you the money.
돈은 내가 빌려줄 테니까
얼른 병원에 가서 그것 좀...
Just go to the hospital and
let's just get that thing...
pushed back in.
밀어 넣어
Thank you, but it'd take me
forever to pay you back.
고맙긴 하지만 그 돈은
평생 가도 갚기 힘들어
I don't want that
hanging over my head.
내가 부담스럽잖아
Besides, when my
insurance kicks in...
게다가 건강보험이 되면
공짜수술도 받을 수 있어
I can get all the free
operations I want.
I'll probably start
with that laser eye surgery.
라식 수술도 받아볼 생각이야
- 얘들아
- 어서 와
What's going on?
왜 그래?
Joey's got a hernia, but it's nothing
a little laser eye surgery won't fix.
조이가 심각한 탈장인데
라식 수술로는 안 나을 거야
I'm telling you,
if I put my hand on my stomach...
봐, 손으로 배를 만져도
그렇게 아프진 않아
it doesn't hurt that bad.
Hey, maybe you'll die!
야, 너 죽을지도 몰라
Chandler, I'm scared.
챈들러, 나 무서워
No, we can go together.
나랑 같이 가면 되겠다
너무 오래 버티진 마
난 금요일 전에 뜨니까
Just don't wait too long, because I'm
out of here sometime before Friday.
But I don't want to die.
난 죽고 싶지 않아
신나잖아, 귀신이 돼서
얘들을 괴롭히는 거야
It'll be fun. We'll come back
and haunt these guys!
오, 잠깐
Wait. Could I come back and haunt Monica
and Rachel when they're in the shower?
모니카랑 레이첼이 샤워할 때
나타날 수도 있겠네?
-That's my girlfriend.
-Hey, I'm dead!
내 여자친구야
난 죽었어
-Give me them!
-No, they are mine!
- 이거 놔
- 싫어, 내 거야
- 네가 훔쳤잖아
- 네가 훔친 거야
-You stole them from me!
빨리 내놔!
Give me them!
그냥 하나씩 가질까?
Just wanna each take one?
Yeah, that seems fair.
We never use them.
그게 좋겠다
쓰지도 않을 건데
Look, I really need
some help, okay?
얘들아, 나 좀 도와줘
어째서 내 입에서
영국식 억양이 나오지?
Why did I have to speak
in a British accent?
What do I do?
어떡할까?
엄마아빠한테 전화해봐
Why don't you call
Mummy and Daddy?
I'm serious! Someone's gonna find out and
then they're never gonna offer me a job.
난 심각해, 가짜라는 게
들통나면 정교수직은 없어
Why don't you phase it out?
Yeah, phase the accent out.
서서히 없애는 거야
그럼 오빠가 미국 생활에
잘 적응한다고 생각하겠지
People will think you're
adjusting to life in America.
Come on.
No one will even notice.
아무도 눈치 못 챌 거야
어차피 듣지도 않을 텐데
They're probably not even
listening to you.
They're not listening to me?
듣지도 않는다고?
물론 듣고 있지
Of course they're listening to you.
모두 듣고 있어
Everybody listens to you.
Monica, do you think I should
try this phasing-out thing?
모니카, 정말 서서히
없애면 될까?
I think you look fine.
지금도 잘하고 있는데 뭐
Whenever you're ready.
- 시작하세요
- 그러죠
Hey, Timmy.
얘야, 티미...
I've got a surprise...
멋진 선물이 있단다
for you.
Hold it.
I'm sorry.
잠깐, 죄송해요
The surprise is a new swing set.
If you could play it less intense.
선물은 그네 세트인데
감정이 너무 강하군요
Oh, yeah. Sure, no problem.
네, 그 정도야 뭐
잠깐만 기다리세요
Just hold on one second.
Hey, Timmy.
얘야, 티미
I've got a surprise for you!
멋진 선물이 있단다
망측해라
Oh, my God!
So that's why I feed my dog
Purina One.
그래서 저희 집 개한테는
'퓨리나 원'을 먹이죠
Pick up a bag today.
오늘 한 봉지 들고 가세요
-That's where you pick up the bag.
-Exactly.
거기서 봉지를 들어올려요
바로 그거죠
The line is, "Pick up a bag,"
so you need to pick up the bag.
들고 가라는 대사니까
봉지를 들어올려요
Or I could just point to it.
그냥 손가락으로
가리키는 건 어때요
어쩌고저쩌고... 퓨리나 원
오늘 한 봉지 가리키세요
Purina One. Point to a bag today.
I didn't get it, did I?
저 떨어졌죠?
- 네
- 그럼요
안녕하세요
Joey Tribbiani.
조이 트리비아니입니다
'남자' 오디션이 있다고 해서
I'm here to audition for "Man."
You mean "Dying Man."
'죽어 가는 남자' 말이죠?
맞습니다!
-Do it one more time.
-Really? Really? Okay.
- 한 번 더 해보자
- 정말? 정말?
좋아
Hello, Ross? This is Dr. McNeely
from the Fake Accent University.
로스, 가짜 억양 대학의
맥닐리 박사입니다
We'd like you
to come onboard full-time!
본교 정교수로 초빙합니다
- 안녕
- 어서 와
Listen to this!
들어봐
My reading was wrong.
I'm not going to die.
점괘가 틀렸나봐
난 안 죽을 거야
Really? How do you know?
정말? 어떻게 알아?
그 심령술사가 죽었거든
My psychic is dead!
She must have read
the cards wrong.
카드를 잘못 읽은 거야
I'm sorry.
너무 안됐다
내가 죽는 것보단 낫지
Better her than me.
Hey, let's bake cookies!
야, 쿠키 굽자!
실버컵 스튜디오
Listen, I'm really glad
you got the part.
배역을 따내서
정말 다행이다
고마워
Are you sure you can do this?
근데 할 수 있겠어?
- 그럼, 데려다줘서 고맙다
- 뭘
And thanks for coming with me.
And thanks again
for helping me take a shower.
샤워 거들어준 것도
다시 한 번 고맙고
Now, is that
"never talking about it again"?
그 사건은 영원히
묻어두기로 했잖아
- 저 왔습니다
- 네, 기다리고 있었어요
We're ready for you.
This is Alex.
He'll be playing your son.
조이, 이쪽은 알렉스
아들 역할이죠
Hi, Alex.
안녕, 알렉스
보시다시피
바지춤에서 손 뺐습니다
As you can see, my hands
are not in my pants.
그렇군요
All right, Alex.
Now, when Joey says his line...
자, 알렉스
조이가 '엄마를 부탁한다'고
말할 때 우는 거야, 알았지?
"Take good care of your mama, son,"
that's your cue to cry. Got it?
All right, let's do this.
좋아요, 그럼 갑시다
Scene five, take one.
신 5, 테이크 1
And action!
준비, 액션
Take good care of your mama, son.
엄마를 부탁한다
Come on, son.
제발, 아들아
Your mama's good people.
너희 엄마 좋은 사람이야
Cut! Alex, remember, you're
supposed to cry.
컷
알렉스
여기서 넌 울어야 돼
이번엔 울 수 있지?
Can you cry for us this time?
그럼요
All right. From the top.
좋아, 처음부터 다시
Scene five, take two.
신 5, 테이크 2
Take 36 is up.
테이크 36 준비
Let's try this again.
좋아요, 다시 갑시다
You ready, Joe?
준비됐나요, 조이?
잠깐만요
One thing, is it all right
if I scream...
액션 사인 나기 전에
비명 좀 질러도 될까요?
right up until
you say, "Action"?
그래요
Sure.
-Action!
-Take good care of your mama, son.
- 액션!
- 엄마를 부탁한다
Cut!
컷!
I'm sorry. Why don't you lift up your
shirt? Take a look at this, kiddo.
실례합니다
조이, 셔츠를 올려봐
이걸 봐라, 꼬마야
We have a crying child!
Roll the damn cameras!
울음보 터졌다!
카메라 돌려요!
- 여보세요?
- 로스 선생 계십니까?
-Hello, is Ross there?
-No, he's not. Can I take a message?
지금 없는데
전하실 말이라도
Yes, this is Russell,
Ross' divorce lawyer.
네, 저는 이혼담당
변호사 러셀입니다
연락을 안 하는 걸 보니
Since I haven't heard from him, I
assume he's giving the marriage a try.
혼인을 파기할 뜻이
없는 것 같아서요
Ross got married again?
로스가 또 결혼했나요?
헉? 아니 되오!
All right, keep going.
We are phasing the accent out.
좋아, 이대로 가자
억양을 차츰 없애는 거야
Phasing it out.
"So without retesting their results
in the laboratory...
만약 당시 실험실에서
재분석을 하지 않았다면
the team would never
have identified...
연구에 참여했던 과학자들은...
the initial errors
in their carbon dating...
탄소연대측정법의 오류를
발견하지 못했을 것입니다
analysis."
Were there any questions
at this point?
이쯤해서 질문 없나요?
- 네
- 억양이 좀 이상하신데요?
What's happening to your accent?
Come again? What's this nonsense?
뭐라고요?
무슨 말이죠?
All right. I'm not English.
사실 난 영국인이 아닙니다
I'm from Long lsland.
롱아일랜드 출신이죠
I was really nervous,
and the accent...
너무 긴장하는 바람에
영국식 억양이 튀어나왔어요
just came out.
I'm sorry.
미안합니다
So if we could just
get back to the lecture.
그럼 강의를 계속하죠
Were there any questions?
질문 있습니까?
About paleontology?
고생물학에 관해서?
난 그저 첫인상을 좋게
심어주려고 했던 건데
I was just trying to make
a good first impression.
Obviously, I screwed up. But what
you guys think of me is important...
그게 잘 안 된 듯하군요
난 정교수직을 원하기 때문에
여러분의 판단이 중요합니다
because I'm hoping to get
a permanent job here.
So if you'd just give me another
chance to make a good impression..
좋은 인상을 남길 기회를
다시 한 번 줬으면 해요
Ross! Are you crazy?
로스! 너 미쳤어?
내가 아직 네 마누라야?
I am still your wife?
Were you just never gonna tell me?
끝까지 숨길 셈이었어?
너 어떻게 된 거 아냐?
What the hell is wrong with you?
I could just kill you!
내 손에 죽어볼래?
Well, hello, Rachel!
반가워요, 레이첼
You've really done this before?
진짜 전에도 해봤어?
그렇다니까
걱정 말고 마음껏 휘둘러
You just take a big, big swing, okay?
Now, don't hold back.
- 봐주지 말고
- 알았어
- 얘들아
- 어서 와라
What are you doing?
뭐하는 거야?
보험급여 되찾은 걸
축하하는 중이었어
We're just celebrating that Joey
got his health insurance back.
Oh, all right.
그거 좋지
See? Now let's try one without the helmet.
봤냐?
이제 헬멧 벗고 해보자